const EASY_DATA = `[
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950246",
      "correctAnswer": "Avocado",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Cucumber",
        "Tomato",
        "Mango"
      ],
      "question": "Which Is The Main Ingredient Of Guacamole?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624c60bc50d1a5e051325a70",
      "correctAnswer": "Japan",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Turkey",
        "Spain",
        "Estonia"
      ],
      "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Sushi?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "general_knowledge",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951557",
      "correctAnswer": "Texas",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Florida",
        "California",
        "Georgia"
      ],
      "question": "Which US state is most associated with Chilli Con Carne?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink",
        "food",
        "us_states"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624c60d150d1a5e051325a75",
      "correctAnswer": "Mexico",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Bhutan",
        "Japan",
        "Brazil"
      ],
      "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served a taco?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950234",
      "correctAnswer": "Ronald Mcdonald",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The King",
        "Donald Burger",
        "Meato"
      ],
      "question": "Who is McDonald's mascot?",
      "tags": [
        "business",
        "advertising",
        "fictitious_characters",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624c60f550d1a5e051325a7f",
      "correctAnswer": "Scotland",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Estonia",
        "Hungary",
        "Thailand"
      ],
      "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Haggis?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "631e50a1a11f90a3bf2a3bf9",
      "correctAnswer": "Green",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Red",
        "Blue",
        "Purple"
      ],
      "question": "What colour is wasabi?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "colours",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950298",
      "correctAnswer": "Michelin Star",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "North Star",
        "Flavour Star",
        "Prestige Star"
      ],
      "question": "What Type Of Star Is Awarded To Restaurants Where The food Is Of Exceptional Quality?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "general_knowledge",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950248",
      "correctAnswer": "Apple ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Blackberry",
        "Strawberry",
        "Banana"
      ],
      "question": "Which fruit is traditionally covered with toffee at a fairground?",
      "tags": [
        "food"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951555",
      "correctAnswer": "Samosa",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Pakora",
        "Curry",
        "Bhaji"
      ],
      "question": "What name is given to an Indian deep fried triangular pastry?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "india",
        "pastry",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95023f",
      "correctAnswer": "Al dente ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Tartilli",
        "Forte Benne",
        "Parpa Delle"
      ],
      "question": "Which Italian phrase is used to describe pasta cooked only until it offers a slight resistance when bitten?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951635",
      "correctAnswer": "Bread",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Cheese",
        "Fruit",
        "Nut"
      ],
      "question": " What type of food is pitta?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "general_knowledge",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    }
  ]`

const MEDIUM_DATA = `[
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502ce",
      "correctAnswer": "Ultra Heat Treated ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Unbonded Holisticly Treated",
        "Unified Head Treatment",
        "Unilateral Heavy Tarry"
      ],
      "question": "What Do The Initials U.H.T Refer To In Relation To Milk",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624c60a650d1a5e051325a6a",
      "correctAnswer": "Iran",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "North Africa",
        "Vietnam",
        "Italy"
      ],
      "question": "Where in the world would you most expect to be served Chelo Kebab?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951602",
      "correctAnswer": "A ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "B",
        "C",
        "D"
      ],
      "question": "Carrots Are Rich In which Vitamin?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502b8",
      "correctAnswer": "Egg Nog ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Milkshake",
        "Cappuccino",
        "Lassi"
      ],
      "question": "What Milky Drink Is Often Drank On New Years Eve?",
      "tags": [
        "drink",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624ab083348a461bfc67067e",
      "correctAnswer": "The Americas",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Southeast Asia",
        "Africa",
        "Europe"
      ],
      "question": "From which part of the world do squashes originate?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951603",
      "correctAnswer": "Flower Buds ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Fish Eggs",
        "Berries",
        "Fermented Tubers"
      ],
      "question": "Capers Are Derived From What?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "639898545c9a75021f31047a",
      "correctAnswer": "Red wine",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Brandy",
        "Port",
        "Beer"
      ],
      "question": "What type of alcohol is traditionally used in the French dish 'Coq au Vin'?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink",
        "drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951601",
      "correctAnswer": "Sturgeon ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Salmon",
        "Trout",
        "Herring"
      ],
      "question": "Which fish does caviar come from? ",
      "tags": [
        "fish",
        "food",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "625006cb0d86c8f685d80efd",
      "correctAnswer": "Tubular pasta",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Ribbon pasta",
        "Shaped pasta",
        "Strand pasta"
      ],
      "question": "What type of pasta is macaroni?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "italy",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515c8",
      "correctAnswer": "Potato dumplings",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Raw beef",
        "Pickled turnip",
        "Carrot sauce"
      ],
      "question": "What is gnocchi?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "words",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950279",
      "correctAnswer": "England ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The Netherlands",
        "Belgium",
        "France"
      ],
      "question": "Which Country Is The Source Of Stilton Cheese?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624ab06dc64ce21c11f06e9a",
      "correctAnswer": "Central America",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Europe",
        "The Middle East",
        "South America"
      ],
      "question": "From which part of the world does papaya originate?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    }
  ]`

  const HARD_DATA = `[
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "627164581ba117625baac959",
      "correctAnswer": "Jinmen Gaoliang",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Bourbon",
        "Riga Black Balsam",
        "Chibuku"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these is a popular drink in Taiwan?",
      "tags": [
        "drink",
        "alcohol"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950274",
      "correctAnswer": "Gin ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Rum",
        "Vodka",
        "Whiskey"
      ],
      "question": "Which alcoholic drink would you need to make the cocktail Tom Collins?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950265",
      "correctAnswer": "Ireland ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Germany",
        "Denmark",
        "Finland"
      ],
      "question": "Which country does one associate with 'Barmbrack'?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515d3",
      "correctAnswer": "Swift ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Lark",
        "Blackbird",
        "Heron"
      ],
      "question": "From Which Birds Nest Is Birds Nest Soup Made?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502a6",
      "correctAnswer": "Claret ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Burgundy",
        "Shiraz",
        "Cabernet Sauvignon"
      ],
      "question": "What name was given to the light, clear wine developed in medieval times along the coastal valleys of the Gironde river in the Bordeaux region?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502e8",
      "correctAnswer": "Eight ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Two",
        "Four",
        "Sixteen"
      ],
      "question": "How many standard bottles of wine are in a Methuselah? ",
      "tags": [
        "drink",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950293",
      "correctAnswer": "Plum ",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Cherry",
        "Peach",
        "Raspberry"
      ],
      "question": "What type of fruit is a damson?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "625006520d86c8f685d80ee2",
      "correctAnswer": "Strand pasta",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Soup pasta",
        "Ribbon pasta",
        "Tubular pasta"
      ],
      "question": "What type of pasta is bigoli?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "italy",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "627164b91ba117625baac971",
      "correctAnswer": "Estonia",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Finland",
        "Macedonia",
        "Bolivia"
      ],
      "question": "In which country is vana tallinn a popular drink?",
      "tags": [
        "drink",
        "alcohol"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "627164b51ba117625baac970",
      "correctAnswer": "Riga Black Balsam",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Unicum",
        "Sangria",
        "Chapalo"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these drinks would you associate with Latvia?",
      "tags": [
        "drink",
        "alcohol",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624ab0d4348a461bfc67069d",
      "correctAnswer": "China",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Central America",
        "Africa",
        "South America"
      ],
      "question": "Where in the world are apricots originally from?",
      "tags": [
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    },
    {
      "category": "Food & Drink",
      "id": "624c6152badf21197f98f774",
      "correctAnswer": "Chicken Machboos",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Ambuyat",
        "Pepperpot",
        "Pho"
      ],
      "question": "Which of these dishes is most associated with Bahrain?",
      "tags": [
        "food",
        "food_and_drink"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "regions": [],
      "isNiche": false
    }
  ]`


  export {
    EASY_DATA,
    MEDIUM_DATA,
    HARD_DATA,
  }